{
    "subject": "resource/CCTV_New_Year's_Gala",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Lang_Kun",
    "human_readable": "The director of CCTV New Year's Gala is Lang Kun.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.949960470199585,
            "question": "Who is the director of CCTV New Year's Gala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6841078400611877,
            "question": "Who are some other prominent figures involved in the CCTV New Year's Gala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6594257950782776,
            "question": "What is the significance of the CCTV New Year's Gala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.580250084400177,
            "question": "What year was the CCTV New Year's Gala first held?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.559159517288208,
            "question": "How does the CCTV New Year's Gala reflect Chinese culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.525456964969635,
            "question": "What are some popular elements featured in the CCTV New Year's Gala?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5018232464790344,
            "question": "What impact does the CCTV New Year's Gala have on viewers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4633152484893799,
            "question": "What is Lang Kun known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.448755145072937,
            "question": "Which event does Lang Kun direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3803711533546448,
            "question": "Is Lang Kun involved in television production?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of CCTV New Year's Gala is Lang Kun.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1208_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which event does Lang Kun direct?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1208_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Lang Kun known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1208_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact does the CCTV New Year's Gala have on viewers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1208_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1208_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1208_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1208_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1208_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1208_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1208_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1208_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1208_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1208_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1208_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the document mentions that Lang Kun is a candidate for the director position, it does not state that he has been selected.  The article says Feng is reportedly chosen as the general director. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context, Feng has been selected as the general director of the CCTV New Year's Gala, not Lang Kun. Therefore, the statement that the director of CCTV New Year's Gala is Lang Kun is incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "According to the provided context, while Lang Kun, Sun Bin, and Lyv Yitao are candidates for assistant director positions, no information suggests that Lang Kun has been selected as the general director of the CCTV New Year's Gala.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context information states that the candidates for director include Lang Kun, Sun Bin, and Lyv Yitao, but does not confirm any of them as the chosen director.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "there are multiple candidates mentioned (Lang Kun, Sun Bin, and Lyv Yitao) to be the co-director with Feng, but no specific selection of Lang Kun as the director.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context mentions that Feng is reportedly selected to act as general director of the annual gala, and provides a list of potential directors including Lang Kun, but does not confirm Lang Kun as the actual director.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}